export const questionsData = [
    {
      Question: 'Q1. What is ReactJS?',
      Options: ['Server-side Framework', 'User-interface framework', 'A Library for building interaction interfaces', 'None of the Above'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'A Library for building interaction interfaces'
    },
    {
      Question: 'Q2. What is the name of React.js Developer ?',
      Options: ['Tim Lee', 'Jordan Lee', 'Jordan Mike', 'Jordan Walke'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Jordan Walke'
    },
    {
      Question: 'Q3. Who Develop React.js?',
      Options: ['Google', 'Apple', 'Facebook', 'Twitter'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Facebook'
    },
    {
      Question: 'Q4. What is Babel?',
      Options: ['A transpiler', 'An interpreter', 'A Compiler', 'Both Compiler and Transpiler'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Both Compiler and Transpiler'
    },
    {
      Question: 'Q5. In React what is used to pass data to a component from outside?',
      Options: ['setState', 'props', 'propTypes', 'render with arguments'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'props'
    },
    {
      Question: 'Q6. Number of elements, a valid react component can return?',
      Options: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
      CorrectAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      Question: 'Q7. Keys are given to a list of elements in react. These keys should be.... ',
      Options: ['Unique in the DOM', 'Unique among the siblings only', 'Do not requires to be unique', 'None of the Above'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Unique among the siblings only'
    },
    {
      Question: 'Q8. What do you call a React component that catches JavaScript errors anywhere in the child component tree?',
      Options: ['Error bosses', 'Error catchers', 'Error helpers', 'Error boundaries'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'Error boundaries'
    },
    {
      Question: 'Q9. Why might you use a ref?',
      Options: ['To directly access the DOM node ', 'To refer to another JS file', 'To bind the function', 'To call a function'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'To directly access the DOM node '
    },
    {
      Question: 'Q10. What package contains the render() function that renders a React element tree to the DOM?',
      Options: ['React', 'DOM', 'ReactDom', 'Render'],
      CorrectAnswer: 'ReactDom'
    }
  ];